Good morning and welcome, everybody.
I'm Jenny Stewart and I'm the Staff Manager here at the exhibition centre.
We're expecting this year's International Travel Exhibition to attract over 10,000 visitors a day, ladies
and gentlemen,
and you are among the two hundred extra staff recruited to help look after
them.
Now, to help things run smoothly, we have divided you into four teams-the blue
team, the green team, the red team,
and the yellow team.
So first I'll explain how the teams are divided up,
and then we'll be giving you colour-coded T-shirts so we can identify you more
easily.
First of all, those who will be looking after the phones
and handling all calls regarding the exhibition, you will be on the red team.
Now, we've also put the entrance staff on the red team
and you'll be stamping the entrance tickets and giving out publicity leaflets, OK?
Those of you involved in distributing entrance tickets will be on the yellow team
and we've also put those of you who'll be staffing the information booths around
the conference centre on the yellow team,
so you'll be getting a yellow T-shirt.
Now, most of the hospitality staff have been put in the blue team,
so the chefs among you and the kitchen hands will all need a blue
T-shirt,
but,
because of the sheer numbers, all waiting staff will be on the yellow team,
and this includes the bar staff among you.
Those who will be monitoring and directing the traffic in the car parks are
on the green team,
so you'll need to get a green T-shirt.
This year we've also employed a considerable number of attendants to direct the human
traffic around the conference centre.
Now, you'll be working in the exhibition hall at all times, giving directions
and generally helping people whenever you can,
and you will be in the red team,
so please collect a red T-shirt.
Right, now that everyone knows what team they're in, we'll get on with the orientation
and training programmer and first I'll run through the rest of today's programme,
which you should have in front of you,
so that you can get a general idea of what else is in store
today.
This introduction finishes at 9.30 and then you'll be hearing from Anne Smith.
Anne works in the accounts department on level two and she looks after all
temporary staff,
and so she is the person to see if you have any problems regarding
pay.
Anne will be explaining when and how you get this.
She will also be handing out your tax forms.
And I will just stress that all tax forms must be completed
and returned to Anne before your pay can be processed.
Following Anne's talk you'll hear from Peter Chen, our Conference Manager,
and he will be going over a plan of the conference centre with you,
which will help you to orient yourselves.
He will also go through the security arrangements with you
and show you the fire exits.
Then at 10.30, there will be a coffee break in the staff canteen,
which is located down on the ground floor.
Now, after the break we'll be moving to a different location for a video
presentation,
so instead of coming back here, we'd like you all to go to Lecture
Room three-one-one.
You'll find it on this same level, just down the hall,
and there you will be shown a video about important safety issues in the
workplace, called Safety at Work.
We'll finish off the morning with lunch,
which should give everyone a chance to meet and get to know each other,
and we'll be serving you a buffet lunch in the Main Hall,
which is on the first floor, from 12.00 o'clock.
After lunch you'll be divided up into your teams to meet your team leaders
and we're hoping to be all finished by 3.00 so I won't delay you
any longer,
and I'll hand over to...